webmarketingsettlement.com 2015-03-25

# PRIVACY NOTICE

PRIVACY NOTICE
GCG PRIVACY NOTICE
I.   PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
     Garden City Group, LLC (“GCG“) Policy Concerning Confidential Information
     and Comprehensive Written Information Security Policy is designed to prevent
     the unauthorized disclosure of non-public personally-identifiable information,
     including social security numbers and other non-public information that either
     may identify an individual or may be used together with other information to do
     so, in GCG’s possession (“PII”). GCG’s personnel are required to follow specific
     security procedures for storing, using, and disposing of PII provided to
     GCG. GCG may grant access to such PII only to individuals who reasonably
     need access to accomplish the purposes for which GCG collected the PII. GCG
     policy prohibits the unlawful disclosure of PII. GCG considers all such
     information to be Confidential Information that may be used only for the
     purposes for which it was provided to GCG, and may not be disclosed or
     disseminated unless there is a business need to do so.
II.   POLICIES CONCERNING PII COLLECTED BY GCG
      Pursuant to court-ordered procedures, GCG,in its designated capacity as
      a settlement, claims or notice administrator, often collects PII through the
      return to GCG of proof of claim forms that GCG disseminates. Such
      proof of claim forms may be disseminated via the United States Postal
      Service, via the internet or on GCG’s proprietary website, located at
      http://www.gardencitygroup.com (the “Site”), or through other websites that
      GCG may design and maintain in connection with an administration
      project. GCG also may collect PII directly through the Site without the use of a
      proof of claim form.
      The proof of claim forms that GCG disseminates, in whatever form they
      may take, may require persons or entities to furnish to GCG PII, such as birth
      dates, tax identification or social security numbers, and account information,
      only to the extent that such PII is deemed by the relevant court or client to
      be reasonably necessary for GCG to process, investigate or reasonably
      validate proofs of claim; for GCG to provide case administration services; or for
      GCG to comply with applicable laws, regulations or GCG policies and
      procedures. GCG’s clients and any courts that may be supervising the matter
      ultimately are responsible for determining whether it is reasonably necessary
      for GCG to collect certain types of claimant information in connection with
      GCG’s administration of any particular administration project.
      GCG’s clients or courts that may be supervising any particular settlement
      administered by GCG may determine that, to participate in that settlement, a
      person must submit a completed proof of claim form. In such settlements,
      claimants must provide the information, including any PII and any other
      confidential information, required on the proof of claim form or they may not
      participate.

A. Collection, Use and Disclosure of PII
1. The PII GCG May Collect
   To participate in a settlement administered by GCG, a person or entity may be
   required to provide PII in order to access the Site and the information available
   through it, to receive notice of a particular matter or to participate in a
   settlement. To do so, a person may need to provide to GCG his or her name,
   email address, mailing address, phone number and other personal information. He
   or she may be asked in areas of the Site or on a particular proof of claim form for
   additional information that relates to particular settlements or other projects for
   which a court has authorized GCG to provide services. Depending on the
   circumstances of the project, a person or entity may be asked to provide financial
   or other PII that GCG needs in order to evaluate, process and pay his, her or its
   proof of claim. In certain settlements, the failure to provide the PII will prevent the
   person or entity from participation.
2. Children’s Privacy
   GCG does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13
   through the Site. If a person is under the age of 13, he or she is advised not to use
   the Site or to provide information to GCG. If GCG becomes aware that it has
   received PII from a child under the age of 13, GCG will make commercially
   reasonable efforts to delete that information from its database.
3. How GCG May Use PII
   GCG will retain and use PII to accomplish the purposes, such as communicating
   with the person or entity who provided it or processing his, her or its proof of claim,
   for which such PII was provided to GCG, and shall retain such PII only so long as
   is necessary to accomplish such purposes subject to, as applicable in each case,
   orders of the court, contractual provisions concerning retention and destruction of
   documents, and the direction of GCG’s clients. GCG also may use that PII to
   customize the services GCG provides, and to comply with applicable laws,
   regulations and GCG policies. All hard copy and electronically stored PII shall be
   destroyed in compliance with court orders, contractual provisions with clients or
   directions from clients, as applicable. Such destruction shall be conducted in a
   manner that prevents loss, theft, misuse, or unauthorized access to the
   information.
4. When GCG May Disclose PII
   When required to do so, GCG will disclose PII to the Internal Revenue Service (the
   “IRS”) in connection with Internal Revenue Code income reporting
   requirements. Except for such IRS reporting and the limited situations discussed
   in this Privacy Notice, GCG will not share PII with any persons or entities unless
   they are under contract with GCG to provide services in connection with the
   administration project for which the PII was provided to GCG, or unless the court
   supervising the administration project has authorized them to receive such
   PII. Thus, GCG may share PII as needed to fulfill requests to process proofs of
   claim or otherwise provide noticing and/or administration services. For example,
   GCG may be required to provide information to the court in which a case is
   pending, to the litigants in that case and to their counsel.

   GCG also reserves the right to disclose PII it acquired online if GCG believes, in
   good faith, that such disclosure is required by law or that such disclosure may be
   necessary to prevent misuse of the Site. For example, PII provided via the Site
   may be used by GCG to identify, contact and/or bring legal action against
   someone whose activities may threaten (either intentionally or unintentionally) to
   infringe upon the rights or property of GCG, of other visitors to the Site, or of
   anyone else.
   GCG does not rent, sell or otherwise disclose for any other purpose any PII.
B. Compiled Information
1. Statistical Information
   From time to time, GCG may gather general non-personal statistical information,
   including information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a
   specific page, how long they remain on that page, and the hyperlinks, if any, on
   which they “click.” Through the use of technological features such as “IP
   addresses” and “cookies” (both of which are discussed in greater detail below),
   GCG may collect that kind of information to determine which areas of the Site are
   visited most frequently, and to enhance the Site for visitors. GCG also may
   compile that data in order to describe to our clients, the courts or others, or to
   respond to a government and/or legal requests, the use of the Site. Any such
   compiled data will not personally identify any person, including any visitor to the
   Site.
2. IP Addresses
   An “IP address” is a number that is automatically assigned to a computer
   whenever it is used to surf the web. Web servers, computers that “serve up” web
   pages, automatically identify a computer by its IP address. GCG records IP
   addresses for purposes of system administration, to report statistical information
   and to track the use of the Site. When a visitor requests pages from the Site,
   GCG’s servers log the visitor’s IP address. It is not GCG’s usual practice to link IP
   addresses to any PII. Although a visitor’s session is logged, the visitor typically
   remains anonymous to GCG. GCG reserves the right to identify a visitor through
   an IP address, however, if GCG believes doing so is necessary to enforce
   compliance with the Site’s policies or to protect GCG, visitors to the Site or others.
C. Links to Other Sites
   Users of the Site are advised that they may be directed to other sites that are
   beyond GCG’s control. Links may take a person from the pages of the Site to
   unaffiliated sites. Those other sites may transmit their own “cookies” (pieces of
   information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping
   purposes) to visitors, collect data or solicit personal information. Visitors to the Site
   also are advised that the privacy policies of those other sites may differ
   significantly from the policies described in GCG’s Privacy Notice, and that GCG is
   not responsible for the privacy practices of those other sites and cannot guarantee
   the security of any personal information that may be collected there.

D.   Security
     Protecting the security of PII is very important to GCG. When such PII is
     transmitted to GCG, it is protected by a “firewall” (a combination of hardware and
     software that helps keep unauthorized visitors from accessing information within
     GCG’s computer network), as well as industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets
     Layer) encryption. Once GCG receives a transmission, GCG will take reasonable
     precautions to keep that information secure on its systems. While GCG strives to
     protect privacy, however, no data transmission over the Internet may be
     guaranteed to be 100% secure. GCG, therefore, cannot warrant or guarantee the
     security of any PII transmitted to GCG online, or be responsible for the theft,
     destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of that PII.
E.   Changes to This Notice
     The terms of this Privacy Notice may change from time to time. If a change is
     made, the “Last Modified” date located at the bottom of this Notice will be updated
     to reflect the amendment. Visitors to the Site are advised to check periodically for
     any changes. The continued use of the Site after GCG posts changes to this
     Privacy Notice will indicate acceptance of those changes.
F.   To Unsubscribe
     If a person does not wish to receive e-mails from GCG, he or she may unsubscribe
     by contacting GCG at unsubscribe@gardencitygroup.com.
III. QUESTIONS?
     Any questions regarding GCG’s Privacy Notice may be directed to Dan Lane,
     Vice President, Quality Assurance, at daniel.lane@gardencitygroup.com or to
     Stacey Fishbein, Associate General Counsel and GCG’s Privacy Officer,
     Stacey.Fishbein@gardencitygroup.com. © 2013 GCG. All rights reserved.
                                                         Rev.1 April 9, 2007
                                                         Rev. 2 July 17, 2008
                                                         Rev. 3 September 30, 2009
                                                         Rev. 4 April 27, 2010
                                                         Rev. 5 November 27, 2012
                                                         Rev. 6 February 11, 2015
